(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
♫I never know what love is like♫
♫All my life, never once have I experienced it♫
♫No one to take that place in my heart♫
♫But now that I’ve met you, my heart begins to glow♫
♫What feeling is this? Why is my heart fluttering?♫
♫And I just can’t control it.♫
♫What happened to my heart right now?♫
♫I can’t control it when you’re around♫
♫This heart…it stops at you♫
♫ Is this love? Is that what they call it?♫
♫ When my heart starts to waver♫
♫ Like a stream of water slowly pouring over my heart♫
♫ From dusk till dawn, you’re never far from my sight♫
♫ Or is this love? Are you that someone...♫
♫ ...who’s destined to be with me?♫
♫ Is this really happening ? I really want to know ♫
♫‘Cos you now hold a special place in my heart♫
[Waves of Deception]
[Previously]
Do you really think I don’t know who she is?
I’d known it since the very first day I met your sister.
You used my sister.
You’ve never loved her all this time, haven’t you?
Well, it’s just a game. Don’t take it personal.
You heard everything, right, Lada?
Lada.
I’m so stupid. I should’ve listened to you
Fah sent us an SOS saying that you’re in need of help.
Give me a hug.
It’s all right.
Don’t go anywhere tomorrow.
Dad has invited Mr. Huad and Kirk for dinner at our place.
And don’t do anything that might embarrass Dad again.
Understood.
If you come to our place, you must try the fish.
It surely looks tempting.
Wow, awesome!
If you don’t like anything, feel free to comment. I’ll give your feedback to our chef.
Oh, I wouldn’t dare.
Oh, I wouldn’t dare. Isn’t he a five-star hotel chef?
It doesn’t matter how many stars he’s got.
If anyone in my family says i
t’s not good, then it’s not.
The chef must listen and try to improve.
I really like it when you call us ‘family’.
It makes my heart feel so warm.
But if you want my comment, maybe you should take better care of my future daughter-in-law.
She looks a bit too thin.
Will she be able to give me a grandson as her firstborn?
Of course, you’ll surely get that.
Lada, what Zodiac year you said you were born in?
Year of the Tiger.
Tiger?
A girl born in the Tiger year isn’t quite a good match for Kirk.
With such a strong fate, she’d only make her husband feel inferior.
I don’t think so.
Lada was born early in the year.
If we count it the Chinese way, it was actually a golden year.
- Really?
- Yes.
That’s great!
Dad! Dad, I don’t believe in those things.
It’s all up to me and Lada whether we can go well together
You might think she’s too thin.
But I think she’s quite hot.
You’re a sweet talker.
- So, Kirk.
- Yes, Bro.
Saying that, does that mean you like her?
Well, if I were to be honest,
I more than like her. It’s love at first sight.
I can’t continue eating.
The food is too cheesy—makes me want to puke.
Lada.
Lada! Lada! Get back here right now!
Dad, did I say something wrong?
Let’s carry on with our meal.
Det, I’m begging you.
Lada doesn’t like Kirk. Please don’t force her into this marriage.
They’ll love each other after living together for a while.
Look at Wat and Mei. They’ve gone through it and are still together now.
Just marry her off to Kirk,
so that she won’t be a burden to my family anymore!
If Lada is a burden to you, I can look after her myself.
We won’t bother you again.
What? What was that? Say it again!
If looking after me and her makes you think you can do anything to us,
then I’ll look after her myself.
Don’t!
If you don’t stop, I’ll call the police.
Although she’s your wife, you’ve never shown her any respect!
You didn’t even sign a marriage certificate with her!
If you hurt her, it won’t be just a domestic abuse.
It’s man assaulting woman.
Lada!
You think you’re better than me?
Then pack your things and get the hell out of here!
Yes, I’m going to take Mum out of here now.
Make sure you have enough cash to pay for mum’s lawsuit.
Hey!
You have no idea, don’t you?
The reason your mother always stays home and hardly goes out to see anyone, do you know why?
- No! Please stop!
- It’s because she killed someone!
That’s not true! Don’t listen to him.
It was an accident! I didn’t kill anyone!
Stabbing someone to death with a knife, you call that an accident?
- You know it too.
- Know what?
That he was trying to rape me!
I had to protect myself. It was just a self-defense!
You slept with that bastard.
And you were afraid he’d tell me.
That’s why you killed him.
Right, Mon?
No, it’s not true! It’s not true, Lada.
Who would believe you?
All you have are your stupid words
and a knife you used to kill him which I still have it with me.
What? You’ve kept it all this time?
Why did you do that?
Why did you keep it? Why did you keep it?
How could you do this to me?
I wouldn’t have done it,
if it weren’t because your ungrateful child,
had chosen to be with the bloody Watin Group!
You think I don’t know why you don’t want to marry Kirk?
It’s because you love that freaking Adisorn’s daughter, isn’t it?
You can’t wait to get out of here and go live with the Watin Group, don’t you?
I’m not welcomed there. Miss Apo already knows who I am.
Then just listen to Dad and marry Mr. Huad’s so
Lada. Listen to me, sweetie.
You don’t have to do it.
You’ve done enough for me.
Whatever will be, just let it be, dear.
Wat.
- Yes, Dad.
Call the police.
Are you sure, Dad?
I’ll do it.
Your happiness at the cost of your mother going to jail,
if you think that’s worth it, then go on.
If I agree to marry him, all of this will be over, right?
Nam! I’ve got news.
About what?
About Chonlada, of course.
How’s she? Where’s she now?
Is she okay? Is she having any problems?
Please calm down and listen to me.
She’s…
She’s what?
Right now, she’s at Mr. Pheemdet’s house.
And is she okay? How is she doing?
She’s fine but…
Hurry up and say it!
Promise me you’ll calm down, okay?
Calm down about what? Just say it!
Chonlada is getting married.
Doing this won’t make anything better, do you know that?
Please don’t be mad at me, Nate.
Apart from Mum, you’re all I have now.
If even my best friend is mad at me, I’ll have no one else left in my life.
I told you to love yourself more. But look what you’ve done.
You let your dad marry you off with some guy you barely know.
Are you trying to ruin your own life just because you’re heartbroken?
I’ve always been helpless.
Never get to voice out my own thoughts.
That’s why I’m often used by others
and be rid of once they find me useless.
Whether it’s Dad, Pat, or…
I thought you said you’d heed my advice.
Why can’t you love yourself more, Lada?
I do love myself.
But I love my mother more.
Every decision in my life has never been easy—you also know that.
What if I make mistake again?
This time, it’s not just me. But Mum will be in trouble too.
May you both have lots of kids together.
- Please always forgive each other.
- Yes, Dad.
May you two always find happiness in life.
Yes, Mum.
This one is for you.
And this one is for you, Lada.
Kirk.
Yes?
Please take good care of her for me.
Yes, Dad. Please don’t worry.
Lada, be a good wife to him.
And don’t make me wait too long to hold my grandson.
Okay?
What a perfect match.
Please take care of her for me.
Of course, I'll take good care of this daughter-in-law.
Let’s take a picture together.
Ready?
One, two, three!
Lada.
You and Kirk still haven’t signed a marriage certificate yet.
You can still change your mind, dear.
Please trust my decision, Mum.
[Door shutting]
Dad said it’s time.
But it’s not time for an evening party yet.
Dad wants Lada to sign a marriage certificate with Kirk first.
But I thought Dad said it’d be after the party.
It’s a matter of benefits. That’s why it can’t wait.
Let me get this straight, Lada.
You’re not marrying for love. This is purely for business interest.
Hurry up now.
Lada! There’s a commotion at the hotel.
Why do the police need to conduct a search here?
The police said they’ve found a suspicious bag in the kitchen next door.
What happened?
My team and I will go down and pretend to inspect the bag to buy you some time.
You and Fai should hurry to room no.888. It’s Chonlada’s bridal suite.
Thanks a lot for helping me.
This is nothing. The hard part is how to get her out of here.
No matter what, I’m going to take Lada out of here with me.
I’m not gonna let her marry someone she doesn’t want to.
We’d better hurry up then.
This is the Wachara Group’s den, I don’t trust anything.
Let’s hurry up and get it over with.
Why did you come up here?
Isn’t the suspicious bag downstairs?
So, what are you guys doing here?
- Call the hotel staff.
- Yes, sir.
Plan B, now.
[Emergency alarm]
What the heck is it this time?
You two go check that side. See why the alarm goes off. Go now.
- Wait! Hold on.
- Evacuate everyone out of the hotel.
- Let’s go.
- Wait!
What happened?
[Commotion]
Help! Fire! Fire!
Quickly! Move!
Hurry up! Move it!
Sis, you go ahead. I’ll keep watch here.
Hasn’t Lom gone a bit too far?
Nam wants to steal the tiger’s cub from its den, so we must make a scene to lure the tiger out.
Hope Nam can rescue Lada and make it out of here.
[Lada: I’m sorry, Dad. I can’t marry him. I’m sorry.]
[Two weeks later]
I’m home!
You’re back? What have you got there?
Everything on your list, Mum.
Whoa, that’s a lot.
- And also…
- Let me see.
Mum!
What?
I forgot to buy your favourite noodles.
I’m sorry.
It’s all right, sweetie. Come, let’s go inside.
Not yet.
Look, the tools kit.
I bought them just in case.
I’m going to fix the door today.
Oh, Lada.
When Wat showed us this place, he also said he’d find someone to fix the door for us.
You don’t have to do it, dear.
That’s all right. I don’t want to trouble him.
He already helped us a lot—renting this homestay for us before,
the wedding and even kept it a secret from Dad.
I’m so grateful I don’t know how I could repay him.
So, if there’s anything I can do, I want to do it myself.
Lada.
But this place is quite far away. I don’t think anyone can find us, right?
Are you afraid Dad will find us?
I just want you to be able to live your life freely from now on.
It’s all right, Mum.
Come on, let’s go eat.
I really love spending time with you.
So, when are you going to fix the door?
You have to help me too. The spare parts are so tiny.
Are you sure you can fix it?
Of course.
Why is the toolbox so big?
Here you go!
Put it over here, sweetie.
Oh, it’s cooked. Right on time.
Give me the plate, dear.
The other day when we went to the market, I saw you keep staring at the instant noodle.
So, I thought you must be craving for it.
Wow, it looks amazing.
These noodles are quite good.
That means you’re starting to open up for something plain and useless.
It’s because you made them.
What’s wrong, sweetie?
Something must have gotten into my eyes.
I’ll go wash first.
Hello, Lada.
Lom?
Sorry for intruding. The door isn’t locked, so I just walked in.
End of Loneliness?
I also know someone who’s feeling lonely right now.
Maybe she should come here so that she’ll no longer feel lonely.
How did you know I’m here?
Actually, I must say it took me too long to figure out you’re here.
Please answer me, how did you know I’m here?
Careful, it’s hot.
This one looks good to
Clear soup is mine. Blood soup is yours.
You shared my photo to your police friends’ chat group?
Nope. I just have many police friends in almost every province.
I’m sorry. But if I hadn’t done that, I would’ve never found out you’ve moved to live this far.
That’s why I’ve moved here—because it’s far from everyone that I know.
But for someone, it might not be far at all.
I don’t think I have to tell you why I’ve moved all the way here.
And I don’t want anyone to know about it too.
Mr. Pheemdet already sold off his Wachara Group’s branch in Hua Hin.
That has nothing to do with me.
But if Mr. Pheempat comes looking for you,
you might no longer feel safe here. Do you still think it has nothing to do with you?
In the worst case, Mum and I can just move somewhere else.
Somewhere so far away no one can find us.
Are you really mad at my sister?
Or do you probably hate her now?
I’m a bad person. I lied to your sister
and even took advantage of her father’s trust in me to benefit my own family.
But in the end, you didn’t do it though.
Nam and Uncle also don’t blame you.
They know you were used.
You were even forced to get married.
That’s why Nam raided the hotel to rescue you.
Miss Apo was also at the wedding?
All this time, we’ve put our own families first.
Don’t you think it’s time to start anew and do what our hearts truly want?
Your mother killed someone!
It’s not true, dear. It was an accident!
Don’t listen to him!
Stabbing someone to death with a knife, you call that an accident?
might be able to run away from the Wachara Group.
But I still have Wacharadecha blood running in me.
You’re also well aware that Watinwanich and Wacharadecha are archenemies.
I don’t think Miss Apo and I could start anew together.
If you keep doing this, my mum and I will have no choice but to move away.
And please tell Miss Apo that if she really forgives me, please let me go.
Please don’t look for me, I’m begging you.
Who’s it, sweetie?
She thinks our homestay looks nice, so she just stops by for more information.
Please feel free to look around.
- Let’s go eat.
- Okay.
I’m starving.
Please feel free.
Are you hungry, dear?
You heard everything, right?
The peace ambassador has failed.
I’m sorry.
You don’t have to apologise, Lom.
It’s me who has to thank you for helping me find Lada.
Just leave the rest to me.
I’m out to buy noodles for you, Mum—to make up for the other day.
I’ll hurry home when I’m done.
Okay, Mum.
Excuse me? These sunflowers and tulips, how much are you selling them?
I’m afraid they are all taken.
Would you mind taking my thought of you instead?
Wait, Lada!
I’m so glad to see you, Lada.
Since that day you’ve been gone, I couldn’t contact you at all.
You don’t answer my call or even read my text.
I just want to explain about what you heard that day.
You’re getting me wrong.
The truth is…
You already know who I am.
Please leave me alone.
What if I can’t leave you alone?
That’s none of my business.
Because I don’t have any feelings for you anymore.
Do you get it?
[Car horn honking]
Mum.
Hm?
Someone will come to install an online customer reception for our backend work today.
Okay.
Did you buy these tulips?
No, someone from a flower shop sent them.
Didn’t you order them?
Oh, you didn’t?
Unless I say so, please don’t accept anything delivered here next time, Mum
[Our love will never die.]
Here you go.
This cake is so good. Have some first.
Thank you, Mum.
But I can go get it myself.
Let me do something for you too, sweetie.
Thank you.
Yes, dear.
Is this our homestay webpage?
Pretty, isn’t it? I’ve only opened it for two days but there are over a hundred followers now.
That’s considered a lot for a newly opened homestay like us.
Wow, over a hundred?
That’s a lot indeed.
But will your dad and Pat know it’s us if they see this webpage?
They won’t. I’m not using my real name.
I use our company name as a homestay owner and also as a payee.
I also created a new email and got a new phone number.
There’s absolutely no way they’d find out.
You’re so smart, my girl.
[Message notification]
[Hi, I’d like to book two rooms for this Saturday.]
What’s that sound?
Mum, we’ve just got a booking!
Booking?
Yes, at our homestay!
Really? How many guests? How many rooms do they want?
But we only have two rooms decorated. Will they be okay with it?
Calm down, Mum. Let me see the booking details first.
Our guest’s name is Miss Napa. She wants to book two rooms for this Saturday.
This Saturday?
We have customers now!
Geez, will she let me book a room at her homestay?
It’s only been operated for two days, Sis. No one would hear about it yet.
Besides, you’re using a new account.
There’s no way she’d know it’s you. Don’t worry.
Hey, she has replied.
See? What did I just say?
Told you not to worry.
Sorry, our homestay is fully booked at the moment.
What?
It’s been opened for only two days.
People hardly know about it, plus this is not during a high season.
Are you serious?
How?
Lada, both rooms at our homestay are still available, why did you reject the booking?
I’ll let you in on another secret.
When Nam was young, all the friends in her class had their names ended with an ‘a’.
So, she secretly changed her name to Napa.
Napa? Why Napa?
I’ll go arrange the flowers, Mum.
[Drone flying]
[I miss you]
[Forgive me]
Just wait, I’ll make you praise me for doing a great job one day.
Good, I’ll be waiting.
One bowl of wonton soup, please.
Why did you order a wonton soup for me?
Because you don’t eat spicy food.
Where are you?
I’ve come too far to turn back.
Lada.
It’s not just about me and you anymore.
If I turn back now, I’ll get the others into trouble too.
I can’t do that.
If it’s about your mother’s case,
Mr. Pheemdet has always lied to her.
How did you know about that?
That man who tried to hurt your mother, he’s still alive.
What do you mean?
That day when I went to look for you at the hotel.
Miss Apo.
I already know what Miss Wayo’s planning to do.
Miss Preem told me everything.
I’m the one who told her to let everyone know that Lada is in this room.
Miss Preem said she’s got an informant who’s close to Lada.
It’s you.
That’s right. And according to Miss Wayo’s plan, after the fire alarm goes off,
I was supposed to take Lada out of the hotel to see you.
But when I came in here, she was gone.
Hold on, Miss Apo.
I went to see Lada at her place yesterday and I saw her mother, Aunt Mon, crying.
Aunt Mon kept saying that Lada has to do this because of her.
Why?
Aunt Mon used to commit a crime.
Lada’s father found out and has been using it to threaten her mother.
Lada and Aunt Mon have never lived their lives the way they want to.
If you finally find Lada and able to make it up with her,
please look after her for me.
I asked Lom to check if there’s anything we could do with this case.
It turns out the man your father kept telling your mother that he was dead…
was actually just injured.
Your father was the one who paid for everything
including the hush money to keep that man silent.
This means Dad has been lying all this time just to have control over Mum?
But you don’t have to worry. She’s free from now on.
You can also rest assured that your father won’t be able to use this to threaten your mother again.
Thank you. If there’s a chance, I’ll repay your kindness for helping me.
But if you’ll excuse me.
Please give me a chance, Lada.
Aren’t you also sad that we’re apart like this?
I actually wanted to give you this ring on your birthday.
But things happened and I lost the chance.
Now that we’ve met again,
I’ll show you that from now on, no matter what happens,
I will never be afraid.
The only thing I’ll be afraid of
is that I might never see you again.
I promise that from now on, I’ll love and cherish you better than before.
Can we please get back together?
I’m sorry, Miss Apo.
♫Have you ever loved me? Please let me know♫
♫If those hugs you gave me meant anything at all♫
♫I don’t want to imagine it alone. Do you also feel the same?♫
♫Forget about that promise and tell me honestly♫
♫If you’ve ever loved me at all♫
[Next Episode]
You’re no longer needed here.
Miss Preem.
Yes, Big Boss?
Boss has resigned.
What happened? Why did she quit?
I know she rejected you but my girl isn’t someone who would sit around being miserable like this.
I don’t know what to do anymore, Dad.
Miss Apo.
What are you doing here?
♫ Since the day you came into my life, I start to realise…♫
♫ What it’s like to be someone who matters ♫
♫ Feeling so warm whenever I see you♫
♫ Who often stays close to me♫
♫ I just want you to know♫
♫ This feeling that’s happening inside♫
♫ I don’t want to hide it anymore♫
♫ I guess I’ll have to tell you♫
♫ You’re the one that change my life ♫
♫ Make me feel more important than anyone♫
♫ Thank you so much for making my life meaningful♫
♫ How lucky I am to have you♫
[Waves of Deception]